fits.me 2017-10-04

# Privacy Policy | Fits.me

#### **WHO WE ARE**

**This Privacy Policy is issued by** **Fits.me Holdings Limited (“** **Fits Me** **”, “** **we** **”, “** **us** **”), registered in England company number 07871517 and whose registered address is Cardiff House 2nd Floor, Tilling Road, London, NW2 1LJ, United Kingdom** **.**

#### **INTRODUCTION**

This Privacy Policy explains what kinds of personal information we collect at Fits Me, how we use it, who we might share information with (including when we might send information overseas), and your rights in relation to the information we collect (including how you can find out what personal information we hold about you).

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

In this section, we explain the different types of personal information that we may collect or hold about you, depending on whether you are a client using our fit recommendation software services (“ **Services** ”), or an individual who visits our website at [www.fits.me](http://www.fits.me/) (“ **Website** ”) or uses one of our fit recommendation tools on a client website (“ **Fit Recommendation Tools** ”) **:**

#### 1\. Client information

If you sign up with us as a client, we may collect, store and process the following information about you:

**Contact information:** We collect your contact information (name, job title, postal address, telephone number and email address) when you enter that information online to register as a client either through our Website, or client portal, or provide it to our sales team. If you have signed any documents with us, we may also store your signature.

**Billing information:** If you are a client that has chosen to pay for our Services by credit card or direct debit, then our third party payment processors will collect and store your credit card or bank account details when you provide these for payment purposes.

**Service administration information:** We may track which of our Services you use, how you use our Services, how often and for what purposes you contact our teams or support helpdesk, and other administrative information relating to your use of the Services.

#### 2\. Other information

We may also collect, store and process the following information:

**Contact information:** If you contact us through our website, client portal (including our support helpdesk), or by email, post or telephone, we will store the personal information that you provide to us (such as your name, address, telephone number or email address). We may also keep a copy of any notes that we make about your contact and the content of all correspondence between us, including any emails or messages you send to us.

**Demo information:** If you request a demo of our services, whether via our website or via our sales team, we will collect contact information (name, job title, address, telephone number, email address) from you.

**Automatic log data:** When you use our Services or visit our Website, our computer servers may automatically make a log of certain information, including the date and time of your use, your internet protocol (IP) address, location, the address of the last website you visited, your browser type and settings, what type of device you are using, and cookie data (see below for how we use cookies).

**Fit measurements:** if you use our Fit Recommendation Tools on a client website, you may be required to enter certain information including your height, weight, age and body shape.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We may use your information for some, or all, of the following purposes. We do so only where we have a contract with you, or where you have given us your consent, or where the information is aggregated or anonymised so that it does not identify an individual person.

**Access:** To provide you with access to our Website, or client portal.

**Services:** To provide our Services to you as a client and fit recommendations to you as a user of our Fit Recommendation Tools, including by analysing your use of our Services or Fit Recommendation Tools to improve their performance, functionality and development. To provide aggregated, anonymised analytics of how customers use our Fit Recommendation Tools to our clients.

**Client admin:** To process billing payments, invoicing, and to carry out business administration in relation to your client account.

**Support:** To provide clients with helpdesk support for the Services and to provide clients with updates, fixes and other maintenance.

**Communication:** To respond to any contact, query or request from you. To send you administrative messages and notices. To let you know about changes to the Services.

**Security:** To keep our Services secure and to comply with any law, rule, legal decision or regulation that we are obliged to comply with.

**Analysis:** To understand where our Website visitors and Fit Recommendation Tool users are coming from, what browsers or devices they are using and how often they visit our Website or use our Fit Recommendation Tools. To understand more about the relationships between body shapes, garment sizes, fit preferences and geography.

**Marketing:** To send you news about our Services, including new features or new services, or other marketing information, including information relating to selected third parties. We may send this information by email. You always have the option to opt out of receiving marketing communications at any time either through your online account, or by contacting [support@fits.me](mailto:support@fits.me).

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a small data file sent by us to your computer/device and from your computer/device to us each time you visit our Website or use our Services.

**How to disable cookies:** You can set your browser not to accept cookies. The following websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser: www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. However, some of our Website or Services features depend on us using cookies (for example, so that you do not need to enter your measurements a second time when reusing our Fit Recommendation Tools on different retailer websites) and may not function if you remove the cookies.

We use cookies to improve the functionality of our Website and Services.

#### **SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES**

**Group companies:** Fits Me is part of a group of companies and we may share your information within that group. For example, one of our subsidiary companies provides technical support services to our clients and therefore we will share your information with that company to enable them to provide that support.

**Third party service providers:** We use third parties to help us deliver aspects of the Services, and they may process your information on our behalf. Examples include: web hosting providers, IT systems administrators, payment processors, database solutions providers, electronic network administrators, and professional advisors such as accountants, solicitors, business advisors and consultants.

**Legal obligations:** Sometimes, we may be under a duty to disclose or share your information to comply with any legal obligation or in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions and other agreements or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our clients, or others.

**Anonymised, aggregated data:** **We may** **share** **anonymised, aggregated information with any person, for any purpose. For example, to provide analytics on customer fit selections to our clients.**

**TRANSFER OF YOUR INFORMATION OVERSEAS**

We are part of an international group of companies. We also work with third party service providers in different countries (for example, web hosting, helpdesk software providers, payment processors). Therefore, your information may be transferred outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) and stored, or processed in other countries, as part of our business operations.

**LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Our Website or Services may contain links to third party websites. If you visit a third party website, then you should read the privacy policy of that third party website to understand how they collect and use your personal information. We are not responsible for how any third party website collects or uses your personal information.

**SECURITY AND RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**Security:** We take all reasonable steps to protect your information against misuse, loss, unauthorised access, and disclosure. However, you should note that sending information via the Internet is not 100% secure, so we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you send to us via the Website, the Fit Recommendation Tools, or by email or other internet communication method.

**Retaining your information:** We only retain your information for as long as we need it to provide our Services to you, or as long as is required under our contract with you, or as long as we are obliged to keep it to comply with laws or regulations.

#### **YOUR RIGHTS TO ACCESS AND CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION**

**Your rights:** You have the right to access the information that we hold about you and to ask us to confirm how we use your information. If the information that we hold about you is not accurate, complete and up to date, you may request that we correct this information.

**Making an access request** : To make an access or correction request, please contact Fits Me’s support team at [support@fits.me](mailto:support@fits.me). Generally, we will not charge a fee for providing access, however we reserve our right to charge a reasonable fee if your request is manifestly unfounded, excessive, or repetitive or if you request further copies of the same information.

**Accessing your client account:** If you are a client, you may access, correct and delete certain of your information by accessing your user account, using your unique user name and password. If you want to access your information over the telephone or live chat via our support team, you may be required to identify yourself by confirming your account details.

**Complaints:** You always have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner, which is the UK’s Supervisory Authority for privacy matters. You can find contact details here: https://ico.org.uk

#### **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

By providing Fits Me with your information and using our Services and Fit Recommendation Tools, you consent to the collection, use and sharing of your information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to check our Privacy Policy regularly. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will take effect when they are published on our Website. By continuing to use our Website, Services, or Fit Recommendation Tools after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you will be agreeing to the changes we have made.

This Privacy Policy was last updated in June 2017.
